{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","address":"3242 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Motown Grille Inc","licenseNumber":"221927","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/30/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000C0B35A19FAC054C02077C785AA2B4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44951","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","inspectionDate":"2019-01-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44951","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."},{"inspectionid":"44951","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Behind the Condenser","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44951","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"44951","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Under the Ventilation hood","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"44951","inspectionDate":"1/22/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"seals","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Hot holding cabinet","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42967","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","inspectionDate":"2018-07-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41280","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","inspectionDate":"2018-01-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41179","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","inspectionDate":"2018-01-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41179","inspectionDate":"1/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored with food-contact portion exposed","subProblem":"Not covered","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Single service items","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-01-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store inverted."},{"inspectionid":"41179","inspectionDate":"1/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER & FREEZER","subLocation":"On the floor Food products","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"41179","inspectionDate":"1/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"41179","inspectionDate":"1/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"40706","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","inspectionDate":"2017-11-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"5","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"5","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40706","inspectionDate":"11/2/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"inspectionid":"40706","inspectionDate":"11/2/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"40706","inspectionDate":"11/2/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Light intensity","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"40706","inspectionDate":"11/2/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"wall(s)","subItem":"wall covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"Wall panels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"40706","inspectionDate":"11/2/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sloped to drain","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Floor sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"inspectionid":"40706","inspectionDate":"11/2/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"51622568","name":"Bread Basket Deli Downtown Detroit","violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"door(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622568"}}